{
    "subject": "resource/Roger_Daltrey",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:English_rock_musicians",
    "human_readable": "Roger Daltrey is the subject of Category:English rock musicians.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9292778372764587,
            "question": "Is Roger Daltrey considered a musician from England?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8275323510169983,
            "question": "What other musicians might be categorized alongside Roger Daltrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7739779949188232,
            "question": "What bands or musical groups is Roger Daltrey associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7391462326049805,
            "question": "What genre of music is Roger Daltrey known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6497910618782043,
            "question": "How has Roger Daltrey influenced the music industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5736466646194458,
            "question": "When did Roger Daltrey begin his musical career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5659847259521484,
            "question": "What instruments does Roger Daltrey play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45248663425445557,
            "question": "What is Roger Daltrey's vocal style like?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40349167585372925,
            "question": "Has Roger Daltrey won any awards for his music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25936535000801086,
            "question": "What are some of the most famous songs by Roger Daltrey?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Roger Daltrey is the subject of Category:English rock musicians.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6804_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Roger Daltrey won any awards for his music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6804_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Roger Daltrey's vocal style like?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6804_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What instruments does Roger Daltrey play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6804_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6804_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6804_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6804_149.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6804_160.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6804_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6804_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6804_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6804_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6804_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6804_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the structured JSON response:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nReasoning:\nThe documents provided are all about Roger Daltrey, an English singer, musician, and actor who was the lead vocalist of the rock band The Who. This information is consistent with the category \"English rock musicians\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide substantial information about Roger Daltrey's career as an English singer, musician, and actor associated with the rock band The Who. Given that he is prominently described as a prominent figure in the English rock music scene, it is reasonable to infer that he fits under the category of \"English rock musicians.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}